$SLAppGeneral	General Setting
$SLAppQuests	By Target
$SLAppRingTool	Bond Rings
$SLAppProfile	Profile
	
$CloakFrequency	Activation frequency
$per0sec	per {0} sec
$CloakRange	Effect range(ft)
$BaseChanceMultiplier	Chance multiplier
$BaseChanceMultiplierInfo	Adjust the overall probability. It influences the probability of all registered quests.
	
$SLAppONOFF	ON/OFF
	
$EnableRape	Enable rape
$EnableRapeInfo	When you are refused an approach, rape occurs depending on conditions such as arousal.
	
	
$EnablePets	Enable pets
$EnablePetsInfo	Enable to approach from creature followers (dogs, armord trolls, etc).
	
$EnablePlayerHorse	Enable PC's horse
$EnablePlayerHorseInfo	Enable to approach from "(PC Name)'s horse", Frost, and Shadowmere.
	
$EnableElderRace	Enable "ElderRace"
$EnablePromiseRing	Enable "Bond Ring"
$EnablePromiseRingInfo	Activate the effect of "Bond Ring" to limit the partner of the approach. Please get items from AddItemMenu Mod or console.
	
	
$SLAppArousal	Arousal
	
$LowestArousalPC	PC's lowest arousal
$LowestArousalPCInfo	If PC is less than this arousal value, NPC->PC will not call.
$LowestArousalNPC	NPC's lowest arousal
$LowestArousalNPCInfo	If the caller NPC is less than this arousal value, NPC->PC & NPC->NPC will not call.
$DialogueArousal	Arousal for dialog
$DialogueArousalInfo	A value that is judged to be high in arousal when talking to PC. The dialogue will change with this value as the boundary.
	
$SLAppETC	Etc.
	
$EnableForceThirdPersonHug	Forced third person at hug
$EnableForceThirdPersonHugInfo	When hugging, forcefully make a third person perspective. Please enable it when using Face to face conversation.
	
$OutputPapyrusLog	Output Papyrus Log
	
$RegisteredApproachQuests	Registered quest
$RegisteredQuestsCommonOptions	Common option
	
$SLAppMultiplayPercent	3P probability
$SLAppMultiplayPercentInfo	It is the probability of becoming 3P. It is common setting of NPC-> PC, NPC -> NPC.
	
$RegisteredQuestsOptions	Options for approach quest
	
$AddingPointsNPCPC	Sex to PC
$AddingPointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of approach to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
	
$AddingRapePointsNPCPC	Rape to PC
$AddingRapePointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of rape approach to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
	
$AddingHugPointsNPCPC	Hug to PC
$AddingHugPointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of hug to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
	
$AddingKissPointsNPCPC	Kiss to PC
$AddingKissPointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of kiss to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
	
	
$AddingPointsNPCNPC	Sex between NPCs
$AddingPointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of approach between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
	
$AddingRapePointsNPCNPC	Rape between NPCs
$AddingRapePointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of rape approach between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
	
$AddingHugPointsNPCNPC	Hug between NPCs
$AddingHugPointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of hug between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingKissPointsNPCNPC	Kiss between NPCs
$AddingKissPointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of kiss between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.


$SLAppRingInfo{}	Click to add {} ring to your inventory.
