$SLAppGeneral	General Setting
$SLAppEnabled	Enable
$CloakFrequency	Activation frequency
$CloakRange	Effect range(ft)
$BaseChanceMultiplier	Chance multiplier
$TotalAwarnessRange	Effect range multiplier
$EnablePromiseRing	Enable "Bond Ring"
$EnableRape	Enable rape
$EnableChangeRelationshipRank	Enable Relationship change
$EnableElderRace	Enable "ElderRace"
$OutputPapyrusLog	Output Papyrus Log
$RegisteredApproachQuests	Registered quest
$RegisteredQuestsOptions	Options for approach quest
$AddingPointsNPCPC	Sex to PC
$AddingPointsNPCNPC	Sex between NPCs
$AddingRapePointsNPCPC	Rape to PC
$AddingRapePointsNPCNPC	Rape between NPCs
$per0sec	per {0} sec
$BaseChanceMultiplierInfo	Adjust the overall probability. It influences the probability of all registered quests.
$EnableRapeInfo	When you are refused an approach, rape occurs depending on conditions such as arousal.
$EnablePromiseRingInfo	Activate the effect of "Bond Ring" to limit the partner of the approach. Please get items from AddItemMenu Mod or console.
$AddingPointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of approach to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingPointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of approach between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingRapePointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of rape approach to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingRapePointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of rape approach between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$EnableForceThirdPersonHug	Forced third person at hug
$EnableForceThirdPersonHugInfo	When hugging, forcefully make a third person perspective. Please enable it when using Face to face conversation.
$AddingHugPointsNPCPC	Hug to PC
$AddingHugPointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of hug to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingKissPointsNPCPC	Kiss to PC
$AddingKissPointsNPCPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of kiss to PC. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingHugPointsNPCNPC	Hug between NPCs
$AddingHugPointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of hug between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$AddingKissPointsNPCNPC	Kiss between NPCs
$AddingKissPointsNPCNPCInfo	Increase / decrease the probability of kiss between NPCs. In terms of the probability of calculation, it will always occur if you set it to 100, and it will not occur if you set it to -100.
$LowestArousalPC	PC's lowest arousal
$LowestArousalPCInfo	If PC is less than this arousal value, NPC->PC will not call.
$LowestArousalNPC	NPC's lowest arousal
$LowestArousalNPCInfo	If the caller NPC is less than this arousal value, NPC->PC & NPC->NPC will not call.